http://www.lasiksurgerynews.com/privacy.shtml

Skip to site menu
Recommend this page
Privacy Statement
We respect the privacy of visitors to our website. This policy describes how we gather information from our site's visitors and what we do with it.
How We Collect Information
Our web server automatically recognizes each visitor's IP address, which can be associated with your Internet service provider. This does not provide us with personally identifiable information.
You can visit our website without revealing any information about yourself. Our site does not track, collect, or distribute personal information about you (such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and product preferences) unless you voluntarily input this information, such as when you ask us to e-mail a friend about this site or when you otherwise voluntarily input this information. Any information you input will be used by us only as described in the "How we use information" section of this statement.
We use electronic records to compile statistics about how collectively our visitors interact with our website. These statistics contain no personal information. By voluntarily providing us with information about yourself, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this policy.
How We Use Information
We use the personally identifiable information we collect for internal purposes such as improving our products and services, and sending you e-mail (at your request only) about topics you have specified.
When we conduct research, we may share this information in aggregate form with our advertisers. For example, while we would never say, "Jen Jones regularly receives Botox treatments," we might tell our advertisers, "29 percent of our readers regularly receive Botox treatments."
When you request information from us, the information you provide may be shared with third parties so that they may fulfill your request.
Unless otherwise required by law or if pertinent to a judicial or governmental investigation, personally identifiable information is not shared with other organizations or persons. Should we ever need to make an exception, we will say so at the point where you are giving the information.
Information submitted or provided to us by a website user or any person or entity regarding us or our products or services, including but not limited to ideas for new products or services or modifications to existing products or services, shall be deemed to be non-confidential and we shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute such information to others without limitation or attribution.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files that websites store on your computer's hard drive. When they are supplied from our site, they contain information you have given us and are intended to be a convenience to you. They eliminate the need to enter your name and e-mail address in certain forms on our site. They may also record how often you visit our website, or what pages you looked at, so that we may distinguish how many unique visitors we have, how often we are visited, and how many pages are viewed by each visitor. This information may be provided in aggregate to advertisers (for example, "we had 150,000 unique visitors last week").
This site uses cookies only to store personally identifying information that you have provided to us. They are not capable of obtaining additional personally identifying information.
Children
You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personally identifiable information about visitors under 18 years of age.
Other Sites
You have the opportunity to access other sites from this website, by either clicking on a text link or on an advertisement. Please be aware that when you leave this site, you will enter sites outside the control of Ceatus Media Group LLC, and the privacy policies of those sites are likely to differ from ours. We suggest contacting these sites for relevant information about their data collection.
Wear Glasses/Contacts?
LASIK
LASIK
LASIK Cost
LASIK Recovery
LASIK Risks and Complications
LASIK Risks and Complications
Corneal Ectasia
All-Laser LASIK
Verisyse
Refractive IOLs (Clear Lens Extraction)
Refractive IOLs
Refractive Lens Exchange (RLE)
Need Reading Glasses?
Presbyopia Correction
Presbyopia Correction
Presbyopia
Laser Presbyopia Surgery
Laser Presbyopia Surgery
Multifocal LASIK
PresbyLASIK
IntraCor Laser Surgery
Corneal Implants
Have Cataracts?
Refractive Cataract Surgery
Refractive Cataract Surgery
Laser Cataract Surgery
Cataract Surgery Procedure
Cataract Surgery Cost
Cataract Surgery Recovery
Cataracts
Is it Keratoconus?
Keratoconus
Keratoconus
Keratoconus Treatment
Corneal Ectasia
Collagen Cross Linking
More
Find a Refractive Surgeon
Home
Facebook
Twitter
You Tube
Contact Us   |   Site Map
|   About Us   |   Terms of Use   |   Privacy Statement
© 2008-2016 Ceatus Media Group LLC
Images and text on this site belong to Ceatus Media Group. Copying or reproducing any text or graphics from this website is strictly prohibited by copyright law. Please read our copyright infringement policy.
x
